http://www.expresstimesystems.com/terms_privacy.asp

Go!
WALL DESKS
A Valuable Discount Coupon Code Follows This Warning: The factory for Steel Displays & Racks
will be closed 12-23-20 thru 1-3-21 for employee maintenance(vacations). Orders placed after 12:00p EST 12-21-20 will not ship until 1-4-21 of after. Larger orders need to be placed even sooner. So order early to avoid this delay! Save 15% off your purchase of everything on our site with the exception of Reception Furniture and Wall Desks. Use Coupon Code
HAPPYSANTA.
Excludes sales tax & shipping. Coupon EXPIRES 12/212020 sop Shop Early!!
Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on the site, place an order, enter a contest or sweepstakes, respond to a survey or communication such as e-mail, or participate in another site feature.
When ordering or registering, we may ask you for your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
We also collect information about gift recipients so that we can fulfill the gift purchase. The information we collect about gift recipients is not used for marketing purposes.
Like many websites, we use "cookies" to enhance your experience and gather information about visitors and visits to our websites. Please refer to the "Do we use 'cookies'?" section below for information about cookies and how we use them.
How do we use your information?We may use the information we collect from you when you register, purchase products, enter a contest or promotion, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:
To personalize your site experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
To quickly process your transactions.
To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
If you have opted-in to receive our e-mail newsletter, we may send you periodic e-mails. If you would no longer like to receive promotional e-mail from us, please refer to the "How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us?" section below. If you have not opted-in to receive e-mail newsletters, you will not receive these e-mails. Visitors who register or participate in other site features such as marketing programs and 'members-only' content will be given a choice whether they would like to be on our e-mail list and receive e-mail communications from us.
How do we protect visitor information?We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. When you place orders or access your personal information, we offer the use of a secure server. All sensitive/credit information you supply is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our databases to be only accessed as stated above.Do we use "cookies"?Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like
Google Chrom or Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone by contacting customer service.
Do we disclose the information we collect to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your
personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance
notice, except as described below. The term "outside parties" does not
include
Express Time Systems. It also does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety.
However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us?To modify your e-mail subscriptions, please let us know by modifying your preferences in the "My Account" section. Please note that due to email production schedules you may receive any emails already in production.To delete all of your online account information from our database, sign into the "My Account" section of our site and remove your shipping addresses, billing addresses & payment information. Please note that we may maintain information about an individual sales transaction in order to service that transaction and for record keeping.Third party linksIn an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may include third party links on our site. These linked sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these linked sites (including if a specific link does not work).Changes to our policyIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change. This policy was last modified on
October 16, 2015.
Questions and feedbackWe welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about privacy. Please send us any and all feedback pertaining to privacy, or any other issue.Online Policy OnlyThis online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.Terms and ConditionsPlease also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.Your consentBy using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
About Us
Company Info
Contact Us
My Account
View Cart
Sign In
Order Status
Products
satisfied customers
- - - -ABF Freight Systems - - - ABM Facilities - - - Acura of Orange Park - - - Addison Drywall - - - Alexandria Toyota - - - Alfa Romeo & Fiat of Minneapolis - - - AMA Heating & Air - - - American Electric Power - - - Auto Care Plus - - - Axon Pressure Products - - - Benjamin Moore & Co. - - - Better Electric Inc. - - - Big Country RV Inc. - - - BMW of North America -- - - Bottom Line Military Sales, LLC - - - Boys & Girls Club - - - Brasher's Sacramento Auto Auction - - - Brooklyn Mitsubishi - - - Brumos Porsche - - - Bussani Mobility - - -Caddell Construction - - - Cedar Creek Animal Clinic - - - Coiling Technologies Inc. - - - Colonial Motorcars Ltd. - - - Concours Collision Center - - - Corky's Pest Control - - - County of Henrico - - - Crown Equipment - - - Curry General Hospital - - - Daimler Trucks North America LLC - - - Danfoss Power Solutions - - - Darlings Honda Nissan Volvo - - - DAS Facilities Management - - - Dept. of State - - - Dept. of the Interior - - -Deschutes Brewery - - - Dingwall Ford - - - Diode Tech - - - Dura-Cast Products Inc. - - - East West Martial Arts - - - Edmonson Electric Inc. - - - Elite Manufacturing Technologies - - - Excel Truck Group - - - Express Auto - - - Fish Market Restaurants - - - Florida National Guard - - - FMH Material Handling Solutions - - - FOOTDOCTORS - - - Fram Group - - - Fraserway RV - - - Gehl Foods - - - Geweke Toyota - - - GRAINGER - - - Greenway Dodge Chrysler Jeep - - - H & R Agra-Power - - - Hardin-Jefferson School District - - - Hassett Ford Lincoln - - - Health First - - - Hendrick Buick GMC Cadillac - - - High Plains Dermatology - - -
Holthouse Farms - - - Hydraulic Supply - - - Hypretherm, Inc. - - - Hyundai on Perryville - - - IAC Group - - -ID Doctors, PA - - - III-D Construction - - - Interphase Inc. - - - Jacksonville Citgo - - - Jassim Al-Khori - - - Judson A. Smith - - - Kerneos Inc. - - - Keystone Industries - - - Kirchhoff Automotive - - - KOHLER - - - Lamborghini Newport Beach - - - Legoland Reserve N Ride - - - LEXUS - - - LIFE St. Francis
- -- Long Island Spine Specialists - - - LMR Tire - - - Magnolia Advanced Materials Inc. - - - Manheim Nevada Auto Auction - - - Maserati of the Main Line - - - McLeod Auto Sales - - - Mercedes Benz of South Mississippi - - - Metal Works - - - Metro Transit - - - MidWest Single Source Inc. - - - Milford Regional Medical Center - - - Missoula Bone & Joint - - - Morrey Auto Group - - - Morries Mazda - - - MRL Equipment - - - MV Transmission & Auto Repair - - - New York Life Insurance - - - Nissan North America Inc. - - - Nucelar Fuel Services - - - Nyco Products - - - OFFICELINX - - - Orange County Florida - - - Oregon Reproductive Medicine - - - Owens Corning - - - P.E. McManus MD PC - - - Panel Master LLC - - - Parco Inc. - - -Parker Hannifin - - -
Patrick Buick GMC - - - PCP Motorsports
- - - Pediatric Association - - - PENTAIR - - - People for Animals - - - Phillips Chevrolet - - - Pioneer Industries - - - Portland Precision Manufacturing - - - Premo Roofing - - - Pro Metal Works - - - Provincial Airlines - - - Pron Elementary - - -QUALCOMM - - - Quality Seafood, Inc. - - - Quillen Brothers, Inc. - - - QUIKRETE - - - Ramar-Hall Inc. - - - Republic Services - - - RL Currie Corporation - - - Robert Bosch, LLC. - - - Rush Enterprises - - - RUGER - - - Rusty Wallace Ford - - - Serramonte Ford - - - Sheet Metal Connectors - - - Sierra Truck Body & Equipment - - - Sign Solutions - - - South Austin Marine - - - SRG Global - -
- SSF Scavenger Company - - - Stanford University - - - Stanley Police Department - - - Stoneham Motor Co. - - - StormGuard Restoration - - - Stretch Wrap Systems - - - STRYKER - - - Subaru of Wichita - - - Super Car Guys - - - Tanda Supply - - - The Sign Shop - - - Total Corporate Solutions - - - Tufts Grinding Inc.
- - - Umpires Southeast - - - Universal Truck Equipment - - - USPS - - - US Army - - - US Air Force - - - US Navy - - - US Marine Corp - - - US Coast Guard - - - Valley Ford - - - Valdosta Family Medicine
- - - Valley Medical Center - - - Volkswagen of Marion - - - Volvo of Oak Park - - - WACKER - - - Warren Family Medical Center - - - Wassau Window & Wall Systems - - - WCA Hospital - - - White Oak ISD - - - Wilcox High Velocity, Ltd. - - - Winmar Tisdale - - - Wisconsin Metal Parts Inc. - - - Xcel Energy - - - Xylem Inc. - - - XTC Inc. - - - Yankee Atomic - - - Yeagley's Designs - - - YMCA - - - Yokohama Tire Mfg. - - - Zodiac Aerospace - - - Zorba's Restaurant - - -Zu Audio - - - -
Google Translate
1-800-858-7462
or 321-622-5996 Local
Copyright © 2013 Express Time Systems..
Built with Volusion.
